Guide to the Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory records, 1958-2000.
Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory records
- Series IV Projects
  - NAIC Lab Files
    - FEEDS, 1968-1985
      - Employee Recognition activities, 2003-2011 (Box 50, Folder 31)
      - 2008 National Register of Historical Places (Box 50, Folder 32)
      - Commonwealth of Puerto Rico House of Representatives Resolution for support of NAIC & Cornell to maintain facilities at Arecibo, 12-5-06 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - WORKSHOPS, 2004-2011
    - Asteroid Dynamics Workshop, Feb 2004 (Box 50, Folder 34)
    - "Frontiers of Astronomy with the World's Largest Radio Telescope", Sept 2007 (Box 50, Folder 35)
    - 2008 DPS Meeting, Ithaca, Oct 2008 (Box 50, Folder 36)
    - HF Design Review Meeting, Ithaca, Feb 2009 (Box 50, Folder 37)
    - Focal Phased Array Meeting, July 2009 (Box 50, Folder 38)
    - HF Design Review Meeting, Ithaca, Sept 2009 (Box 50, Folder 39)
    - Arecibo Survey Workshop, Dec 2009 (Box 50, Folder 40)
    - RF2010 Workshop, Groningen, March 2010 (Box 50, Folder 41)
    - Fab Five Fest, Arecibo, March 2011 (Box 50, Folder 42)
  - NATIONAL SCIENCE FOUNDATION (NSF) and NATIONAL AERONAUTICS & SPACE ADMIN. (NASA)
    - General/Other, 1973-00 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - First Upgrade
      - NSF/NASA Proposal: Major Additions & Mods to Suspended Antenna, 1971-74 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - 1st Upgrade Corres., 1971-75 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - S-Band - NSF/NASA Corres., 1971-81 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Weekly Reports to NSF: NAIC Upgrading Project, 1972-75 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Monthly Reports to NSF: NAIC Upgrading Project, 1972-76 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - NSF Proposal: Design & Development of Reflector System, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - SETI, 1982-92 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Subcommittee Review, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Second Upgrade
      - Ground Screen - NSF/NASA funding, 1987-92 (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - S-Band - NSF/NASA Corres., 1988-95 (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - Second Upgrade - NSF/NASA funding, 1986-97 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - Management Plan, March 1991 (Box 51, Folder 13)
      - NSF-NASA Memorandum of Agreement, 8/89 (Box 51, Folder 14)
      - Project Approval Request (PAR) Corres.,1990-97 (Box 51, Folder 15)
      - Trustee Reports, 1991-2000 (Box 51, Folder 16)
      - Real Property, 1993, 1999, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 17)
      - Light Age, Inc. Subaward, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Cooperative Agreement, 1999-2004 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Statements of Work
      - SSOW (Specific Statement of Work) Astronomy, 1999-2005 (Box 51, Folder 20)
      - SSOW (Specific Statement of Work) REU, 1999-2004 (Box 51, Folder 21)
      - SSOW (Specific Statement of Work) S-Band, 1999-2005 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Research Experience for Undergraduates (REU)
      - 1988 REU Proposal (Box 51, Folder 23)
      - 1989 REU Proposal (Box 51, Folder 24)
      - 1992 REU Proposal (Box 51, Folder 25)
      - 2002 REU Proposal (Box 51, Folder 26)
      - Goldsmith-NSF REU/RET Corres., 1992-98 (Box 51, Folder 27)
      - Goldsmith-NSF REU/RET Corres., 1999-02 (Box 51, Folder 28)
      - Cooperative Agreement Amendments, 1991-99 (Box 51, Folder 29)
      - Arecibo REU Program 1972-1980 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Arecibo REU Program 1981-1995 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Arecibo REU Program 1996-2004 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Arecibo REU Program 2005-2011 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - HEATING FACILITY (HF)
      - NSF Site Visit, 7-20-98 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - HF Facility - NSF Corres., 1973-79 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - HF Facility - NSF Corres., 1989-2002 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Visiting Scientist Quarters funding, 1999, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Visitor Center Expansion, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Fiber Optic T-1 high speed internet, Puerto Rican Telephone Co. Subaward, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - NSF Corres. 2000-2005 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Hydrogen Maser Subcontract, Dec 2000 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - NSF's Management Review of Cornell and NAIC, Dec 2002 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - Budget Presentation to NSF, 6/03 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - NSF UAF Management Review, Nov 2003 (Box 52, Folder 15)
      - ATM Task Order, 1998-99 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - XXXX
    - Administrative Files
      - A & W Control
        - Initial Agreement, Original File Number 1.A (Box 65, Folder 1)
        - Amendments, Original File Number 1.B (Box 65, Folder 2)
        - Insurance Certification, Original File Number 1.C (Box 65, Folder 3)
        - Change Orders, Original File Number 1.D (Box 65, Folder 4)
        - Invoices 1-10, Original File Number 1.E (Box 65, Folder 5)
        - Invoices 11-20, Original File Number 1.E (Box 65, Folder 6)
        - Invoices 21-30, Original File Number 1.E (Box 65, Folder 7)
        - Invoices 31-41, Original File Number 1.E (Box 65, Folder 8)
        - Invoices 42-55, Original File Number 1.E (Box 65, Folder 9)
        - Invoices 56-68, Original File Number 1.E (Box 65, Folder 10)
        - Invoices - App. For payment, Original File Number 1.E (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - RSI Bid & Negotiations
        - Structure Upgrade RSI Neg., Original File Number 2.A (Box 65, Folder 12)
        - RSI Proposals, Original File Number 2.B (Box 65, Folder 13)
      - General Conditions
        - Schedule of Values, Original File Number 3.A (Box 65, Folder 14)
        - Subcontractors - RSI, Original File Number 3.B (Box 65, Folder 15)
        - RSI Application For Payment #1, Original File Number 3.C (Box 65, Folder 16)
        - RSI Application For Payment #2, Original File Number 3.C (Box 65, Folder 17)
        - RSI Application For Payment #3, Original File Number 3.C (Box 65, Folder 18)
        - RSI Application For Payment #4, Original File Number 3.C (Box 65, Folder 19)
        - RSI Application For Payment #5, Original File Number 3.C (Box 65, Folder 20)
        - RSI Application For Payment #6, Original File Number 3.C (Box 65, Folder 21)
        - RSI Application For Payment #7, Original File Number 3.C (Box 65, Folder 22)
        - RSI Application For Payment #8, Original File Number 3.C (Box 65, Folder 23)
        - RSI Application For Payment #9, Original File Number 3.C (Box 65, Folder 24)
        - RSI Application For Payment #10, Original File Number 3.C (Box 65, Folder 25)
        - RSI Application For Payment #11, Original File Number 3.C (Box 65, Folder 26)
        - RSI Application For Payment #12, Original File Number 3.C (Box 65, Folder 27)
        - RSI Application For Payment #13, Original File Number 3.C (Box 65, Folder 28)
        - RSI Application For Payment #15, Original File Number 3.C (Box 65, Folder 29)
        - RSI Application For Payment #16, Original File Number 3.C (Box 65, Folder 30)
        - Taitem - Applications for Payment, Original File Number 3.D (Box 65, Folder 31)
        - Payment Summaries, Original File Number 3.E (Box 65, Folder 32)
        - RSI's Insurance, Original File Number 3.F (Box 65, Folder 33)
      - NAIC Administration
        - NAIC Administration, Original File Number 4.A (Box 65, Folder 34)
        - Budget, Original File Number 4.B (Box 65, Folder 35)
        - NSF Correspondence, Original File Number 4.C (Box 65, Folder 36)
        - Miscellaneous, Original File Number 4.D (Box 65, Folder 37)
      - Site Administration
        - General, Original File Number 5.A (Box 65, Folder 38)
        - Project Progress Report, Original File Number 5.B (Box 65, Folder 39)
        - Accidents, Original File Number 5.C (Box 65, Folder 40)
        - Platform Control, Original File Number 5.D (Box 65, Folder 41)
        - Weekly Site Reports, Original File Number 5.E (Box 65, Folder 42)
        - Project Schedule, Original File Number 5.F (Box 65, Folder 43)
        - Site CQC, Original File Number 5.G (Box 66, Folder 1)
        - Safety, Original File Number 5.H (Box 66, Folder 2)
        - Government Furnished Equipment (GFE), Original File Number 5.I (Box 66, Folder 3)
        - Shipment Docs/Log/Correspondence, Original File Number 5.J (Box 66, Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous Invoices, Original File Number 5.K (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - General Requirements
        - RSI Schedules, Original File Number 6.A (Box 66, Folder 6)
        - Surveyor Qualifications, Original File Number 6.B (Box 66, Folder 7)
        - Cutting & Patching GR 1070, Original File Number 6.C (Box 66, Folder 8)
        - Progress Photos GR 1380, Original File Number 6.D (Box 66, Folder 9)
        - CQC Plan 01400, Original File Number 7.A (Box 66, Folder 10)
        - CQC Plan, Original File Number 7.B (Box 66, Folder 11)
        - Site Survey, Original File Number 7.C (Box 66, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Original File Number 8.A (Box 66, Folder 13)
        - Material Sub. & Certs., Original File Number 8.B (Box 66, Folder 14)
        - Data Acquisition Group (DAG), Original File Number 8.D (Box 66, Folder 15)
        - Arecibo Road Repair, Original File Number 8.E (Box 66, Folder 16)
      - Meetings
        - Site Planning Mtg RSI/JM/Nog/Rig, Original File Number 9.A (Box 66, Folder 17)
        - Arecibo Site Meetings (1), Original File Number 9.B (Box 66, Folder 18)
        - Arecibo Site Meetings (2), Original File Number 9.B (Box 66, Folder 19)
        - Arecibo Site Meetings (3), Original File Number 9.B (Box 66, Folder 20)
        - MTG Min 4-21-93 Kickoff and Preconstruction, Original File Number 9.C (Box 66, Folder 21)
        - Meeting 10/19/93 (DC w/RSI), Original File Number 9.D (Box 66, Folder 22)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #1, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 23)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #2, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 24)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #3, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 25)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #4, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 26)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #5, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 27)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #6, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 28)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #7, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 29)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #8, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 30)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #9, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 31)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #10, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 32)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #11, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 33)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #12, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 34)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #13, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 35)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #14, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 36)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #15, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 37)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #16, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 38)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #17, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 39)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #18, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 40)
        - Construction Progress Mtg. #19, Original File Number 9.E (Box 66, Folder 41)
        - RSI/NAIC Weekly Telecons ITH/AO/TPD (1), Original File Number 9.F (Box 66, Folder 42)
        - RSI/NAIC Weekly Telecons ITH/AO/TPD (2), Original File Number 9.F (Box 67, Folder 1)
        - RSI/NAIC Weekly Telecons ITH/AO/TPD (3), Original File Number 9.F (Box 67, Folder 2)
        - RSI-TPD Meeting Minutes, Original File Number 9.G (Box 67, Folder 3)
        - Planning Designing Task GP (2), Original File Number 9.I (Box 67, Folder 4)
        - Planning Designing Task GP (3), Original File Number 9.I (Box 67, Folder 5)
        - Servo Drive System Mtg (Vertex), Original File Number 9.K (Box 67, Folder 6)
        - Taitem - Meeting Minutes, Original File Number 9.L (Box 67, Folder 7)
        - CEC Meeting Minutes, Original File Number 9.M (Box 67, Folder 8)
        - Temcor Meeting Minutes, Original File Number 9.N (Box 67, Folder 9)
        - Miscellaneous Meetings, Original File Number 9.O (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Technical Files
      Arranged Alphabetically.
      - Anchors
        - A4, Original File Number 12.A (Box 67, Folder 11)
        - A8 (1), Original File Number 12.B (Box 67, Folder 12)
        - A8 (2), Original File Number 12.B (Box 67, Folder 13)
        - A12, Original File Number 12.C (Box 67, Folder 14)
        - Anchor Excavation General, Original File Number 12.D (Box 67, Folder 15)
        - General, Original File Number 12.E (Box 67, Folder 16)
        - Anchor Installation General, Original File Number 12.F (Box 67, Folder 17)
        - Backstay/Spherical Washers, Original File Number 12.G (Box 67, Folder 18)
      - Azimuth Rail & Hangers
        - Azimuth Rails, Original File Number 13.A (Box 67, Folder 19)
        - Hangers, Original File Number 13.B (Box 67, Folder 20)
      - Ballast and Cables
        - Ballast, Original File Number 14 (Box 67, Folder 21)
        - General, Original File Number 15.A (Box 67, Folder 22)
        - Pins, Cable Joints, Original File Number 15.B (Box 67, Folder 23)
        - Cable Drape and Tray, Original File Number 15.C (Box 67, Folder 24)
        - Cable Lengths, Original File Number 15.D (Box 67, Folder 25)
        - Ratholes, Original File Number 15.E (Box 67, Folder 26)
        - Installation, Original File Number 15.F (Box 67, Folder 27)
        - Tiedown Removal (Cables), Original File Number 15.G (Box 68, Folder 1)
        - Tensioning (1), Original File Number 15.H (Box 68, Folder 2)
        - Tensioning (2), Original File Number 15.H (Box 68, Folder 3)
        - Tensioning (3), Original File Number 15.H (Box 68, Folder 4)
        - Jacking, Original File Number 15.I (Box 68, Folder 5)
        - Jack Calibration Testing, Original File Number 15.J (Box 68, Folder 6)
        - Fiber Optics, Original File Number 15.K (Box 68, Folder 7)
        - Cable Car, Original File Number 15.L (Box 68, Folder 8)
        - U-Bolts, Original File Number 15.N (Box 68, Folder 9)
        - Cable Dampers, Original File Number 15.O (Box 68, Folder 10)
        - Cable Drag Link, Original File Number 15.P (Box 68, Folder 11)
        - T8 Hairpin U-Bolt Accident, Original File Number 15.Q (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - Cable Carrier/Cable Machine (S-Band)
        - Cable Carrier Correspondence, Original File Number 16.A (Box 68, Folder 13)
        - Cable Machine Design Drawing, Original File Number 16.B (Box 68, Folder 14)
        - Mechanical Engineering, Original File Number 16.C (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - Comissioning and Concrete
        - General Comissioning, Original File Number 17.A (Box 68, Folder 17)
        - Concrete Batch Plant, Original File Number 18.A (Box 68, Folder 18)
        - Concrete Test Results, Original File Number 18.B (Box 68, Folder 19)
        - Concrete General, Original File Number 18.C (Box 68, Folder 20)
        - Grout, Original File Number 18.D (Box 68, Folder 21)
      - Dome
        - Dome Dimensions, Original File Number 19.A (Box 68, Folder 22)
        - Dome Platforms, Original File Number 19.B (Box 68, Folder 23)
        - Dome General, Original File Number 19.C (Box 68, Folder 24)
        - Dome Wind Tunnel Test (1), Original File Number 19.D (Box 68, Folder 25)
        - Dome Wind Tunnel Test (2), Original File Number 19.D (Box 68, Folder 26-27)
        - Dome Desgin, Original File Number 19.E (Box 68, Folder 28-29)
        - Dome Lateral Bracing, Original File Number 19.F (Box 68, Folder 30)
        - Dome Drag Link, Original File Number 19.G (Box 68, Folder 31)
        - Gregorian Elevation Limit Calcs., Original File Number 19.H (Box 68, Folder 32)
        - Collar Truss, Original File Number 19.I (Box 68, Folder 33)
        - Assembly & Erection, Original File Number 19.J (Box 68, Folder 34)
        - Shoring Towers/Scaffolding, Original File Number 19.K (Box 68, Folder 35)
        - Rigging & Lift, Original File Number 19.L (Box 69, Folder 1)
        - EMI/RFI Shielding, Original File Number 19.M (Box 69, Folder 2)
        - Dome Panels, Original File Number 19.N (Box 69, Folder 3)
        - Gregorian Trolleys, Original File Number 19.O (Box 69, Folder 4)
        - Service Platform/Extension, Original File Number 19.P (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Drives
        - Elevation Drives/Design Calcs (1), Original File Number 20.A. (Box 69, Folder 6)
        - Azimuth Drives-Design/Calcs, Original File Number 20.B. (Box 69, Folder 7)
        - Drives System Concept, Original File Number 20.C. (Box 69, Folder 8)
        - Drive System Control System, Original File Number 20.D. (Box 69, Folder 9)
        - Elevation Drive - RFP, Original File Number 20.E. (Box 69, Folder 10)
        - Bidder- Elevation, Original File Number 20.F. (Box 69, Folder 11)
        - Servo Drive System - Addenda, Original File Number 20.I (Box 69, Folder 12)
        - Servo Drive System - Design Rev., Original File Number 20. J (Box 69, Folder 13)
        - Drives Consultant, Original File Number 20.K (Box 69, Folder 14)
        - Tertiary Drive System, Original File Number 20.O (Box 69, Folder 15)
        - Tertiary Drive-Alum Angle PO, Original File Number 20.P (Box 69, Folder 16)
        - Temporary El Drive, Original File Number 20. Q (Box 69, Folder 17)
        - Temporary Az Drive, Original File Number 20.R (Box 69, Folder 18)
        - Az/EL Limit Switches/Emerg Stops, Original File Number 20.S (Box 69, Folder 19)
        - Drive System Dynamics, Original File Number 20.T (Box 69, Folder 20)
        - F&M Mafco Hoist, Original File Number 20.U (Box 69, Folder 21)
        - Feed Module Drive Design, Original File Number 20.V (Box 69, Folder 22)
        - AZ Drive Motor Replacement (Eurodrvs), Original File Number 20.W (Box 69, Folder 23)
        - Servo D. System Acceptance Test, Original File Number 20.X (Box 69, Folder 24)
        - Servo Drive System - RFP, Original File Number 20.G (Box 69, Folder 25-26)
        - Servo Drive System Proposal, Original File Number 20.H (Box 69, Folder 27)
      - Elevation Rack & Rail
        - Rack Gear, Original File Number 21.A (Box 69, Folder 28)
        - Rail Shims, Original File Number 21.B (Box 69, Folder 29)
        - Elevation Azimuth Encoder, Original File Number 21.C (Box 69, Folder 30)
        - General, Original File Number 21.D (Box 69, Folder 31)
      - Feedarm
        - Structural Steel, Original File Number 22.A (Box 70, Folder 1)
        - Ballast Platform, Original File Number 22.B (Box 70, Folder 2)
        - Feed Track, Original File Number 22.C (Box 70, Folder 3)
        - Feedarm Modification, Original File Number 22.D (Box 70, Folder 4)
        - Feedarm Stairway, Original File Number 22.E (Box 70, Folder 5)
        - Feedarm - Top Cord Diag. Install., Original File Number 22.F (Box 70, Folder 6)
        - Clubhouse Removal, Original File Number 22.G (Box 70, Folder 7)
        - 2ndary Bracing Truss Repair, Original File Number 22.H (Box 70, Folder 8)
        - Az Temp. Winch (Le Tourneau), Original File Number 22.I (Box 70, Folder 9)
        - Center Bearing Replacement, Original File Number 22.J (Box 70, Folder 10)
        - Outrigger Platforms, Original File Number 22.K (Box 70, Folder 11)
        - Bracing Truss Reinforcement, Original File Number 22.L (Box 70, Folder 12)
        - CH1 - Lift & Lowering, Original File Number 22.M (Box 70, Folder 13)
      - Feed Module Layout
        - Transmitter Room, Original File Number 23.A (Box 70, Folder 14)
        - Feed Room, Original File Number 23.B (Box 70, Folder 15)
        - Rack Adjustment Mech./Adv. Design, Original File Number 23.C (Box 70, Folder 16)
        - Pillow Block Bearings/Clark Hall, Original File Number 23.D (Box 70, Folder 17)
        - Layout/Wall Design, Original File Number 23.F (Box 70, Folder 18)
        - Door Dimensions, Original File Number 23.G (Box 70, Folder 19)
      - Fitting for Steel Cable and Forms
        - Materials, Original File Number 24.A (Box 70, Folder 20)
        - Anchor Bolt Installation, Original File Number 24.B (Box 70, Folder 21)
        - Request for Change in Bolt Fin Spec., Original File Number 24.C (Box 70, Folder 22)
        - Concrete Collar Forms, Original File Number 25.A (Box 70, Folder 23)
        - Forms for A4, Original File Number 25.B (Box 70, Folder 24)
        - Forms for A12, Original File Number 25.C (Box 70, Folder 25)
        - Forms for B8 and B12, Original File Number 25.D (Box 70, Folder 26)
      - Miscellaneous Hardware & Materials
        - Miscellaneous, Original File Number 26.B (Box 70, Folder 27)
        - Platform Bolt Replacement, Original File Number 26.C (Box 70, Folder 28)
        - Bolt Issues (1), Original File Number 26.D (Box 70, Folder 29)
        - Bolt Issues (2), Original File Number 26.D (Box 70, Folder 30)
        - Test Reports, Original File Number 26.E (Box 70, Folder 31)
        - Fracture Critical Mat. (Subcont Certs), Original File Number 26.G (Box 70, Folder 32)
      - Paints and Platform
        - RSI Paints, Original File Number 27.A (Box 70, Folder 33)
        - Structural Steel, Original File Number 28.A (Box 70, Folder 34)
        - Construction, Original File Number 28.B (Box 70, Folder 35)
        - Mast and Boom, Original File Number 28.D (Box 70, Folder 36)
        - Miscellaneous, Original File Number 28.E (Box 70, Folder 37)
        - Azimuth Trolleys, Original File Number 28.F (Box 70, Folder 38)
        - Steel Design, Original File Number 28.G (Box 70, Folder 39)
        - Stiff Leg Derrick Crane, Original File Number 28.H (Box 70, Folder 40)
        - Electronics Shelter/Quotes, Original File Number 28.I (Box 70, Folder 41)
        - Electronics Shelter/BML, Original File Number 28.J (Box 70, Folder 42)
        - Air Conditioners (Carrier), Original File Number 28.K (Box 70, Folder 43)
        - Handrails, Original File Number 28.L (Box 70, Folder 44)
        - Platform Height, Original File Number 28.M (Box 70, Folder 45)
        - Catwalk, Original File Number 28.N (Box 70, Folder 46)
        - Plans-Stairway/Catwalk/Walkway, Original File Number 28.O (Box 70, Folder 47)
      - Power
        - Dome - Electrical, Original File Number 29.A (Box 70, Folder 48)
        - Drive System Electrical, Original File Number 29.B (Box 70, Folder 49)
        - Feed Module Electrical, Original File Number 29.C (Box 70, Folder 50)
        - Site - Emergency Power, Original File Number 29.D (Box 70, Folder 51)
        - Platform Electrical, Original File Number 29.E (Box 70, Folder 52)
      - Procedures
        - General/Log, Original File Number 30.A (Box 70, Folder 53)
        - #20030 - Paint/Finish, Original File Number 30.B (Box 70, Folder 54)
        - #20049 - Tower Installation, Original File Number 30.C (Box 70, Folder 55)
        - #20051 - Tower Deflector, Original File Number 30.D (Box 70, Folder 56)
        - #20052 - Cable Tension Monitoring, Original File Number 30.E (Box 70, Folder 57)
        - #20053 - Ballast Instal/Plat Level, Original File Number 30.F (Box 70, Folder 58)
        - #20054 - Main Cable Installation, Original File Number 30.G (Box 71, Folder 1)
        - #20055 - Phase 1 & 2 Plat Erect Plan, Original File Number 30.H (Box 71, Folder 2)
        - #20055 - Platform Erection Plan (2), Original File Number 30.H (Box 71, Folder 3)
        - #20057 Carriage House #2 Removal, Original File Number 30.I (Box 71, Folder 4)
        - #20058 Az Track Work Plan, Original File Number 30.J (Box 71, Folder 5)
        - #20059 Phase 1- Feedarm Modifications, Original File Number 30.K (Box 71, Folder 6)
        - #20060 - Outrigger Installation, Original File Number 30.L (Box 71, Folder 7)
        - #20061 Az Track Alignment, Original File Number 30.M (Box 71, Folder 8)
        - #20062 - Elevation Rack & Rail, Original File Number 30.N (Box 71, Folder 9)